{
    "id": "c4232397bdcb4189bf100fa2539286f9",
    "title": "Comparatives And Superlatives",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………….. than her sister.",
            "description": "Most adjectives of one syllable form the comparative by adding –er and superlative by adding –est.",
            "answers": [
                "prettier",
                "more pretty",
                "more prettier"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b71001a9a3a04ce8a465e25558126744"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ………………………… than that.",
            "description": "If the positive adjective ends in -y, the comparative is made by replacing that -y with -i and adding -er.",
            "answers": [
                "more easy",
                "more easier",
                "easier"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "eba3d7536228432d9a12daac37cf1faa"
        },
        {
            "question": "I work hard but he works even …………………….",
            "description": "Harder is the comparative form of hard. ",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "harder",
                "more hard"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e97ee4cbf2c2483d8be728f7fe4d6277"
        },
        {
            "question": "",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ed8a2072f9a141eb9d392f88c7a6514a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ……………………. than her parents.",
            "description": "Adjectives of more than two syllables usually form the comparative by adding more to the positive. ",
            "answers": [
                "generouser",
                "more generous",
                "most generous"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0fcfa0e5ca547deb15ac72ce7c29aff"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was getting ……………………..",
            "description": "The comparative is used when a change is implied. ",
            "answers": [
                "darker",
                "dark",
                "darkest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2253b80df1764857a0da2394af0bfeef"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was the ………………………… day of his life.",
            "description": "Happiest is the superlative form of happy.",
            "answers": [
                "happy",
                "happier",
                "happiest",
                "most happy"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9c053f5ee44b4af79e63d01c6561f40c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Solomon was the ………………….. of all men.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wise",
                "wiser",
                "wisest",
                "most wise"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4800bc12dc4249abbbe6feff8e5d46da"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mark is ………………………… than his brothers.",
            "description": "Richer is the comparative form of rich.",
            "answers": [
                "richer",
                "more rich",
                "most rich"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2c7722140f0f47efad5fdaa6745f4737"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ……………………. than his friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "smarter",
                "more smart",
                "more smarter"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bc87a42b995942a3bd2b29d3b455aea0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………. than her brother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cleverer",
                "more clever",
                "most clever"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "10bd2868a26b4fc7a9cabe7c63c2fc74"
        },
        {
            "question": "His new home is ……………………….. than the previous one.",
            "description": "Adjectives of more than two syllables form the comparative by adding -more",
            "answers": [
                "more spacious",
                "most spacious",
                "spaciouser"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9244edcb8d5048c5a502bd8ee4b0e13b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The task was ……………………….. than I thought.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "harder",
                "more hard"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e53637ae4414590afeae8e75127318e"
        }
    ]
}